Now we are going to talk about tires and tire wears.
This here is a good tire it is a factor tire.
It has plenty of thread in the middle, on the sides.
This tire is off a bike that as you can see it is worn out, this here went way to far.
You should never ride your tires especially when you got strips in the middle where the threads are coming through.
The side walls on this tire are really thin which you don't want to let that happen.
If you don't have a lot of thread on the side you know you have the tendency to slide out in cornering.
Most of your tire would wear out in the middle first because most times you are riding straight.
Just keep your eye out on both the front and the rear tires and check on that cause this here is what keeps your bike from falling in the ground.
So you definitely you want to keep a eye on the thread especially on the sides and the middle.